

Md. Rohul Amin

Software Engineer

- Sha 66/3, Shadhinata Sarani, North Badda, Gulshan, Dhaka, Bangladesh 🛗 05 Jan 1996
- Bangladeshi @ Unmarried in radipu radipu radipu radipu
 ★ radipu.me radipu

CAREER OBJECTIVES

I am a graduate with a bachelor's degree in Computer Science and Engineering. I am experienced in leadership and both front-end and back-end programming languages. Now, I am looking for establishing my career as a .NET developer and team lead. I am a quick learner and willing to learn new technologies to upgrade myself with time. I am working with .NET technology since 2018.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jan 2022 **Software Engineer**

Dhaka, Bangladesh CureTech Ltd 🛮

- Developed web applications.
- Worked on the Engineering part for different projects.
- · Lead a team.

Aug 2021 – Jan 2022

Software Engineer

Sunderland, England

Ginilab Limited

- · Worked on Restaurant Management System.
- · Added new features, and debugging.
- I worked there with .NET Framework, DevExpress, WinForms, Software Design, Fron-end, and Back-end.

Feb 2021 - Jul 2021

Software Engineer

Dhaka, Bangladesh

OurEdu

- · Worked on Account Management System.
- Upgrading the old technology to new technology.
- I have had working here with C# ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, LINQ, CSS, MSSQL, and DevOps.

Jan 2015 - Jan 2021

Head of Information and Communication Technology

Dhaka, Bangladesh Bangladesh Study Forum (BDSF)

- I developed the whole IT system for this organization.
- Lead the IT team
- What have I done: Website development, Organized programs, public speaking, Leadership.

PROJECTS

Feb 2022 - present

Bachao 🗷

Against the rape

- It's a mobile application platform against rape.
- The backend was developed with .NET.
- Technology Used: .NET5, Angular, WebAPI, MSSQL

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022

Restaurant Management System

- It's a desktop software, mostly used in the UK and in the middle east.
- Nearly 200+ restaurants and thousands of customers use this software for ordering food inside and outside the restaurant.
- Technology Used: ASP.NET, DevExpress, WinForms, MySQL, Laragon, HeidiSQL

Feb 2021 - May 2021

Account Management System for Shidlai Ashraf Secondary School

- Enroll new students with details information.
- · Adding new staff and teachers.
- Payroll and tuition fees management.
- Online payment module.
- Technology Used: C#, ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON, LINQ, and following Onion Architecture.

May 2019 - Aug 2019

Penetration, Forensics, Reverse Engineering,

Social Engineering

Library Management System

Technology Used: C#, ASP.NET Core 2.1, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON, LINQ.

SKILLS

Programming Language C, C++, Java, JavaScript, C#, R, Python, TypeScript, Go	Frontend Development VueJS, Angular, HTML5, AngularJS, Bootstrap3, 4, CSS3, Sass
Backend	Database ————
Development	Oracle, MySQL, MSSQL Server, PostgreSQL
.NET Core, .NET, NodeJS, Laravel	
	Source Control ————————————————————————————————————
DevOps	Git, GitHub
AWS, GCP, Azure, Docker, Jenkins, Kubernetes,	
Bash	Interpersonal skills ———————————————————————————————————
	Listening, Caring, Leadership, Self-Motivated,
Data Structure and	Responsibility, Teamwork
Algorithm	
Cyber Security	

EDUCATION

May 2021 Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering

Dhaka, Bangladesh International University of Business Agriculture and Technology

Completed BSc with a CGPA of 3.27 out of 4.00

Jul 2011 - Aug 2013 Higher Secondary Certificate

Dhaka, Bangladesh Cambrian College

Completed HSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

Jan 2009 - May 2011 Secondary School Certificate

Cumilla, Bangladesh Shidlai Ashraf Secondary School

Completed SSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

♂ INTERESTS

Learning New Skills
 Public Speaking
 Reading

Writing
 Leadership

♦ LANGUAGES

Bangla • • • • • English • • • • •